Guide to the Lin Carter Papers, 1900s-2001 and undated RL.11079
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Notes and Reference Materials, 1931-1987 and undated; 3
  - Various book catalogs and book ads of other writer's books, 1981 and undated (Box 8)
    book catalogs (incl. Roy A. Squires), ads, and announcements from various sources
  - Various catalogs (non-books), undated (Box 8)
    includes various catalogs of household items, furniture, etc.
  - Event flyers and programs, undated (Box 8)
    various flyers and programs of non-Carter events
  - Wargaming (serial), Number 1, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Handwritten notes, untitled, undated (Box 12)
    Largely fantasy-related, but includes list "goodbye letters to write before I commit suicide"
  - H. P. Lovecraft to Howard, Robert E. (photocopied postcards, 1930s) (Box 12)
  - The All-Seeing Eye (serial), Vol. 5, number 6, by Manly P. Hall, 1931 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Master Monograph, Temple Section pamphlets, 1940s? (Box 12)
- Personal Documents, 1951-1990s; 4
  - Materials re: Carter's death, 1988-1990s (Box 10)
    Materials from Robert Price, unpublished or in-process manuscript drafts, correspondence re: Carter's literary estate, copyright files
  - The New Kalem Club, 1983 Oct. 22 (Box 8)
    Invitation to first meeting of "The New Kalem Club. A Private, Regularly Scheduled Get-Together of People Who Are Interested in the 'Weird Tales - Arkham House' Culture" on 10/22/1983, "Lines Writ (sic) to Commemorate the First Meeting of the New Kalem Klub, Saturday, October 22, 1983," notes
  - SAGA ("Swordsmen and Sorcerers' Guild of America"), 1967-1968 and undated (Box 8)
    Correspondence and notes
  - The Trap Door Spiders, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 8)
    Member lists from 10/1982, 12/1983, 11/21/1986
  - Agreements with Publishers and Royalties, 1964, 1968-1987 (Box 8)
  - Bills, Receipts, and Invitations by Carter, 1971-1987 and undated (Box 8)
    bills and receipts for rent, utilities, nonemployee compensations and miscellaneous income, and household items (incl. bill for a "New Royal Electric 5000" typewriter, Business Efficiency Agreement, bill for Homemaker/Home Health Services), plane and train tickets, bank documents, and invitation to Halloween and Christmas parties at Carter's home
  - Legal Case (Lincoln Savings Bank vs. Lin Carter), 1981 (Box 8)
    folder originally labeld "House Business" by Carter, legal case re mortgage and building defects
  - Legal Case (Arthur Brandt vs. Lin Carter), 1982-1983 (Box 8)
    legal case about outstanding rent payments
  - Tax Documents, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
    incl. documents re tax returns
  - Official Documents, 1953, 1960 (Box 8)
    Army Papers (discharge papers), Divorce Papers (in Spanish, with English translation)
  - Personal Photographs, 1951, 1958-1959, and undated (Box 8)
    most of the photographs are unlabeled
  - Personal Artifacts, 1956, 1983 and undated (Box 8)
    incl. wallet with Selective Service System Notice of Classification, Social Security ID card, Chase Convenience Card by Chase Manhatten Bank; gift card; name tag of "Brotherhood of Jedi Knights"
  - Copyright search, 1972 (Box 10)